<ipcop>
    <update>
        <version>2.1.0</version>
        <releasedate>2014-02-13</releasedate>
        <size>23985</size>
        <description>setserial, pcmciautils, perl, ppp, openvpn radiusplugin patched&lt;br /&gt;
            cairo recompiled with -O3, isdn4k-utils with -Os -fno-strict-aliasing&lt;br /&gt;
            Add libnetfilter_acct, libnetfilter_log, xz&lt;br /&gt;
            Language updates.&lt;br /&gt;
            Fix SF bug #805, undefined value in connections webui.&lt;br /&gt;
            Upgrade acpid to 2.0.20, arping to 2.13, bash to 4.2.45, bind to 9.8.6-P2, CnxADSL to ..PIM-2.6-2.7
            conntrack-tools to 1.2.2, coreutils to 8.21, db to 6.0.20, dejavu to 2.34, dhcpcd to 5.6.8, diffutils-3.3, dnsmasq to 2.68,
            e2fsprogs to 1.42.8, ethtool to 3.12.1, expat to 2.1.0, fontconfig to 2.11.0, freetype to 2.5.0,
            gawk to 4.0.2, GD to 2.49, gettext to 0.18.3, glib to 2.30.3, gmp to 5.0.5, gnupg to 1.4.13, grep to 2.15, gzip to 1.6,
            hdparm to 9.43, httpd to 2.2.26,
            iproute2 to 3.11.0, iptables to 1.4.20, iptstate to 2.2.5, iputils to s20121221, iw to 3.11, krb5 to 1.10.7,
            less to 458, libffi to 3.0.13, libgd to 2.1.0, libgcrypt to 1.5.3, libnet to 1.1.6,
            libnfnetlink to 1.0.1, libnetfilter_conntrack to 1.0.4, libnl to 3.2.16, libpcap to 1.4.0, libpng to 1.6.7,
            libusb to 1.0.9, libusb-compat to 0.1.4, libtool to 2.4.2, libxml2 to 2.9.1, logrotate to 3.8.6, lsof to 4.87,
            mdadm to 3.3, net-tools to 1.60-p20120127084908, openldap to 2.4.38, openssh to 6.4p1, openssl to 1.0.1e, openswan to 2.6.39,
            openvpn to 2.3.2,
            parted to 3.1, patch to 2.7.1, pciutils to 3.2.1, pcre to 8.33, perl to 5.14.2-21, pixman to 0.32.4, procps to 3.3.8, psmisc to 22.20,
            rp-pppoe to 3.11, rsyslog to 5.10.1, sed to 4.2.2, shadow to 4.1.5.1, smartmontools to 6.2, sqlite to 3.8.1
            tcpdump to 4.4.0, traceroute to 2.0.19, ulogd to 2.0.2,
            usb-modeswitch to 2.0.1, usb-modeswitch-data to 20131113, usbutils to 007, util-linux to 2.22.2,
            zlib to 1.2.8, several Perl CPAN modules.
        </description>
        <previousversion>2.0.6</previousversion>
        <nextversion>2.1.1</nextversion>
        <installdate>INSTALLDATE</installdate>
    </update>
</ipcop>
